Sidney Hillman Foundation Awards 6402
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Sidney Hillman Foundation Awards
2004-2016
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Sidney Hillman Foundation
6402
2.11 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Awards, pamphlets, correspondence, news clippings, photographs.
8817223
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 27, 2015
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, May 11, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6098: Sidney Hillman Foundation Prize for Tom Darcy for His Newsday Cartoons 6098 MB: Sidney Hillman Foundation Banners 6200/004: UNITE HERE Sidney Hillman Foundation Awards 6364: Heather Furnas Collection of Sidney Hillman Foundation Awards Research Materials 6402 AV: Sidney Hillman Foundation Awards Audiovisual Material
8817223
- 2006 Award: "Men of the Pines" (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Prize Winner List (2009) (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 59th Annual Hillman Prizes Program (2009) (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Newspaper Prize: "Deaths in Immigrant Detention" (2009) (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Newspaper Finalist: "Construction Worker Deaths on the Las Vegas Strip" (2009) (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Magazine Prize: "The Nation" Special Issue of "The New Inequality" (2009) (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Magazine Finalist: "Auto Destruct" (2009) (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Broadcast Prize: "Made in LA" (2009) (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Photography Prize: "Birth and Death" (2009) (Box 1, Folder 9)
- 60th Annual Hillman Prize Program (2010) (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Newspaper Prize: "The Fight for Transparency" (2010) (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Photography Prize: "Below the Line: Childhood Poverty in Colorado" (2010) (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Photography Prize: "Ian Fisher: American Soldier" (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Prize Winners List 2011 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- 61st Annual Hillman Prize Program (2011) (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Newspaper Award: "Justice in the Balance" (2011) (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Broadcast Prize: " The Dancing Boys of Afghanistan" (2011) (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Photography Prize: "A Surgery Gone Wrong" (2011) (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Blog Prize: "Feministing" (2011) (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Blog Nomination: "The Great Divergence" (2011) (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Magazine Prize: "The Dark Side of Dairies" (2010) (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Photography Finalist: "In Mexico's War on Drugs" (2010) (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Canadian Hillman Prize Program (2011) (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Canadian Hillman Prize: "Code Red" (2011) (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Canadian Hillman Finalist: "No Running Water" (2011) (Box 2, Folder 5)
- 62nd Annual Hillman Prize Program (2012) (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Hillman Prize Winners 2012 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Newspaper Prize: "The Atlanta Journal-Constitution" (2012) (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Canadian Hillman Prize Program (2012) (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Canadian Hillman Prize: "Scout's Honor" (2012) (Box 2, Folder 10)
- 63rd Annual Hillman Prize Program (2013) (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Hillman Prize Winners (2013) (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Photography Prize: "Beyond 7 Billion" (2013) (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Canadian Hillman Prize Program (2013) (Box 2, Folder 14)
- 64th Annual Hillman Prizes Program (2014) (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Newspaper Prize: "Private Prisons: Profit, Politics, Pain" (2014) (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Canadian Hillman Prize Program (Box 2, Folder 17)